ahead of these Oscars. I want to give myself an award for just watching so many people praise
themselves that are full of shit. I'm watching y'all on panels, stages, I'm watching them on the
TV, just, and they'd be full of shit. Complete farce. And I'm gonna say the thing that folks
know, but they don't really say out loud, which is that this whole thing about like black brotherhood
and black sisterhood and black togetherness in Hollywood, a lot of it is a bunch of bulls**t,
especially the black sisterhood part. And it actually would behoove us to be as loud about
it in real life as we are in celebrating it. One thing about Hollywood, it's gonna big itself up.
Yes, it will. This town don't got no problem celebrating. You know how we'd be like, we need
to learn how to celebrate a victory. We need to learn how to honor ourselves. We need to learn
how to congratulate ourselves. That ain't, that, my dears, is not a problem in this town.
And you know, we should honor ourselves when it's something we actually doing.
But I digress. I want to give myself an award for watching that and not feeling compelled to do like
the climate change activists and stand up and be like, no, because I'd really be restraining.
And then I wonder why I don't get invited places.